<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Indoor on little dog studos</title>
    <link>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/tags/indoor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Indoor on little dog studos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:29:19 +0930</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/tags/indoor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>80s office</title>
      <link>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/posts/80soffice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:29:19 +0930</pubDate>
      <guid>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/posts/80soffice/</guid>
      <description>Step back in time with our Low Poly Modular 80s Office Pack! This meticulously crafted asset pack captures the essence of an open-plan office from the 1980s, featuring warm colors, sharp edges, and vintage technology. Perfect for creating immersive retro environments,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contemporary House</title>
      <link>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/posts/contemporary_house/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:29:19 +0930</pubDate>
      <guid>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/posts/contemporary_house/</guid>
      <description>Elevate your game with our meticulously designed Simple Contemporary House Set, featuring a collection of modern furniture that perfectly complements any contemporary setting. This asset pack is ideal for developers looking to create a sleek, stylish, and nice environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern office</title>
      <link>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/posts/modern_office/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:29:19 +0930</pubDate>
      <guid>https://herio5154.github.io/portfolio.github.io/posts/modern_office/</guid>
      <description>Elevate your game environments with this Low Poly Modern Office asset pack! Designed with a contemporary aesthetic, this pack features bright and airy office spaces filled with plenty of natural light and sleek glass elements. The minimalist design and hand-painted textures ensure a clean and professional look, perfect for modern office scenes. Compatible with all Little Dog projects, this pack is ideal for developers looking to add a touch of sophistication to their games.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
